《六人行》前情题要:
Previously on Friends:
- 艾瑞卡 你还好吧？ - 还好 或许我吃太多了
- Erica, are you okay?     - Yeah, you know, maybe I ate too much.
一直有点胃痛 几分钟就痛一次
I keep getting these stomachaches. They come and go, like, every few minutes.
- 天啊   - 别担心 给她点胃药就好了
- Oh, my God.    - Relax, we'll just get her some antacids.
她不是胃痛 是要生了
She doesn't have a stomachache! She's in labor!
天啊
Qh, my God!
你认为我没跟你单独道别
If you think that I didn't say goodbye...
是因为你没有其他人重要 你就错了
...because you don't mean as much to me as everybody else, you're wrong.
是因为你太重要了
It's because you mean more to me.
- 瑞秋   - 干嘛？
- Rash!    - What?
- 嘿…   - 哈哈
- Hey.    - Ha, ha.
再睡一下吧 我要回家了
Shh. Go back to sleep. I have to go home.
喔 天啊 真是太奇妙了
Oh, God. This was amazing.
真的是啊
It really was.
你学了新招喔
You've learned some new moves.
有个男同事开玩笑 送我一本《性爱指南》
Yeah, well, uh, this guy at work gave me Sex for Dummies as a joke.
- 啊   - 现在笑的人是谁呢？
- Ah.    - Who's laughing now?
我知道
I am.
吸气…吸气…
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
好 很好
Okay. Good.
下次可以换我说 "吸气"吗？
Next time, can I say "breathe"?
不行 上次你说"吸血鬼" 把她吓坏了
No. Last time, you said it like Dracula, and it scared her.
还要再拿些冰块吗？
Can I get you anything? Want more ice chips?
- 不用了   - 好 我 马上回来
- No, I'm okay.    - All right. I'll be right back.
- 你去哪？ - 去上厕所
- Where you going?    - To use the bathroom.
- 你不能留我和她在一起    - 什么？
- You can't leave me alone with her.      - What?
这种社交场合总是让我…
This is exactly the kind of social situation...
浑身不对劲
...that I am not comfortable with.
哪种社交场合你才会对劲？
What kind of social situation are you comfortable with?
只是我跟她从来没有独处过
It's just that we've never spent any time, you know, alone together.
安啦 没事…才怪 我两分钟后就回来
You'll be fine. You won't, but I'll be back in two minutes.
好吧
Okay.
夏天有没有什么计划呀？
So, uh, any plans for the summer?
不晓得 或许参加教会的夏令营吧
I don't know. Maybe church camp.
哈
Ha...
你最好别提到这件事
May not want to mention this.
有没有想过哪个比较糟？
So you ever wonder which is worse?
生小孩还是被踢中胯下？
You know, going through labor or getting kicked in the nuts?
- 什么？ - 喔 这很有意思…
- What?     - Oh, it's just interesting.
永远不会有人知道 因为没人能同时体验这两种感觉
You know, because no one will ever know because no one can experience both.
生命中无解的伟大问题之一
One of life's great unanswerable questions.
谁晓得？
I mean, who knows?
或许有比那些更痛苦的事情呢
Maybe there's something even more painful than those things.
像现在这样
Like this.
- 进来   - 早安
- Come in.    - Morning.
- 嘿   - 那是什么？
- Hey.    - What's that?
我要送摩妮卡和钱德的乔迁之礼
Oh, it's my housewarming present for Monica and Chandler.
- 鸡宝宝和鸭宝宝   - 额
- That's a baby chick and duck.    - Uh-huh.
我叫他们小鸡鸡和小鸭鸭
And I named them Chick Jr. and Duck Jr.
- 真是没料到   - 额 耶
- I did not see that coming.    - Uh-huh. Yeah.
他们一定会喜欢那新房子 后院超大
They'll love it at that new house. It has that big backyard.
等到他们长大之后 就会被送到…
And when they're old, they can go to that farm...
钱德从前把 小鸡小鸭送去的农场
...that Chandler took the other chick and duck to.
- 没错   - 是啊
- Yes.    - Yeah.
- 真可惜那里不开放参观   - 规定如此
- It's a shame people can't visit there.    - That is the rule though.
- 猜怎么着 你快要当舅舅了   - 什么？
- Guess what. You're almost an uncle.    - What?
艾瑞卡进产房了 摩妮卡和钱德正在医院里
Erica went into labor. Monica and Chandler are at the hospital right now.
- 喔 我的天啊   - 我有预感会是个女孩
- Oh, my God!    - I have a feeling it's gonna be a girl.
菲比 你之前就预测过 我儿子会是个女孩
Phoebe, you were sure Ben was gonna be a girl.
你看过他丢球的样子吗？
Have you seen him throw a ball'?
- 瑞秋在吗？ - 她还在睡觉
- Is Rachel here?    - Uh, I think she's still asleep.
你们俩昨晚怎么样？
Hey, hey, hey. How did it go with you guys last night?
她似乎很气你
She seemed pretty pissed at you.
我们谈拢了
We, uh... You know, we worked things out.
笑什么？你们俩怎么了？
What's that smile? Did something happen with you two?
我是不会泄密的人
Hey, I'm not one to kiss and tell.
但我也不是上了床却不说的人 我们上床了
Uh, but I'm also not one to have sex and shut up. We totally did it.
喔 天啊 你和瑞秋？
Oh, my God. You and Rachel?
- 是啊 棒得很   - 这样是什么意思？
- I know, it's pretty great.    - So, what does that mean?
- 你们复合了？ - 这说不好
- Are you guys getting back together?     - Oh, I don't know.
- 我们没怎么讲到话   - 但你会想要复合吗？
- We didn't really get to talk.    - But do you want to get back together?
我不晓得
I don't know.
真太不可思议了 感觉真棒
It was incredible. I mean, it just felt so right.
我抱着她时 我真想永远抱着她不放
When I was holding her, I mean, I never wanted to let her go.
是的 我想要和她复合
Know what? Yeah, I do. I want to be together.
- 呀   - 嘘
- Yay!    - Shh!
呀
Yay!
她还打算去巴黎吗？
So is she still going to Paris?
哇 我倒没想到这点 希望不要
Wow, I hadn't thought of that. I hope not.
今天真是太棒了 你们可能会复合…
This is, like, the best day ever. Ever. You guys might get back together.
摩妮卡和钱德也要有小孩了 还有这些小鸡小鸭…
Monica and Chandler get their baby. There are chicks and ducks...
到处乱跑
...in the world again.
我觉得自己好像在演歌舞剧
Oh. I feel like I'm in a musical.
太阳升起时阳光如此灿烂
When the sun comes up Bright and beamin'
到了夜晚
And the moon comes
- 早安   - 你一定猜不到结局
- Morning.    - Guess you'll never know how it ends.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.    - Hi.
- 嗨 你睡得如何？ - 不错 你呢？
- Hi. How'd you sleep?    - Good. You?
- 很好   - 我想也是
- Good.    - I'll bet you did.
能不能让我们独处几分钟？
Uh, would you guys mind giving us a minute?
当然 小心看着小鸡和小鸭
Sure. Yeah. Just keep an eye on the chick and duck.
小鸡和小鸭？他们不是死了？
Chick and the duck'? Didn't they die...?
"湿了" 对 他们玩水 在农场玩得很开心
Dive. Yeah, they dove. Headfirst into fun on the farm.
所以…
So...
- 早安   - 你也早安
- Morning.    - You too.
- 昨晚真的很棒   - 喔 是啊
- Last night was just wonderful.    - Oh, it really was.
我今早醒来脸上挂着一个大笑脸
I woke up today with the biggest smile on my face.
我知道 我也是 那真的…
I know, me too. It was...
就像那种你认为 永远不可能发生的事…
You know, it was like one of those things you think is never gonna happen.
然后它发生了 正如你心里期盼的
And then it does, and it's everything you want it to be.
是啊 那真的是…
I know. It was just...
最理想的道别方式
It's just the perfect way to say goodbye.
- 再一下就好了 亲爱的   - 喔 天啊 好痛喔
- Just a little bit more, honey.    - Oh, man, this hurts!
- 真有那么痛啊？ - 额
- Is it really that bad? - Uh-huh.
我来踢你胯下 看哪种更难受
I think it's time to kick you in the nuts and see which is worse.
看到宝宝的头了…
The baby's head is crowning.
喔 天啊  那是我看过最美丽的头顶
Oh, my God! That is the most beautiful top of a head I have ever seen.
- 钱德 你过来看   - 没关系 不用
- Chandler, you have to see this.    - I'm okay.
你怎么能错过 这可是你的孩子啊
You don't want to miss this. This is the birth of your child.
- 这是生命的奇迹   - 好吧
- It's the miracle of life.    - All right.
哇 好恶心的奇迹
Wow, that is one disgusting miracle.
开始用力 来吧
Start pushing. Here we go.
肩膀出来了
Here come the shoulders.
是个男孩
It's a boy.
- 他还好吧？ - 很好
- Is he okay?    - He's just fine.
你办到了
You did it.
是个宝宝
It's a baby.
一个美丽的宝宝 还有其他我要假装没看到的东西
A beautiful little baby. And some other stuff I'm gonna pretend I don't see.
- 你要剪脐带吗？ - 好的
- Would you like to cut the umbilical cord?    - Okay.
哇 软软的
Well, that's spongy.
哦…
Oh...
嘿 小帅哥
Hey, handsome.
我会好好爱你 让这世上没有一个女人配得上你
I'll love you so much that no woman is ever gonna be good enough for you.
- 我们好幸运喔   - 是啊
- We are so lucky.    - I know.
他眼睛像你
He has your eyes.
我知道这并不可能 但他真的像
I mean, I know that's not possible, but he does.
- 我们要把他清干净   - 好的
- We'll just get him cleaned up a bit.    - Okay.
喔 天啊 他好漂亮喔
Oh, my God, he's beautiful.
- 真是太感谢你了   - 我很为你们感到高兴
- Thank you so much.    - I'm really happy for you guys.
- 你感觉如何？ - 我好累
- How do you feel?    - I'm tired.
你没有太多时间休息 另外一个马上就要出来了
You don't have that much time to relax. The other one will be along in a minute.
对不起 谁就要从哪里出来了呢？
I'm sorry, who should be along in a what, now?
下一个宝宝应该就快出来了
The next baby should be along in a minute.
我们只订了一个
We only ordered one.
- 你们知道是对双胞胎吧？ - 喔 是啊…
- You know it's twins, right?    - Oh, yeah.
这种表情正是知情的样子
These are the faces of two people in the know.
你们居然不晓得是一对双胞胎 从来没发生过这种事
I can't believe you didn't know its twins. This has never happened before.
哇塞 这可让我觉得好特别 感觉真棒
Well, gosh. That makes me feel so special and good.
你晓得是双胞胎？
Did you know it was twins?
知道啊 诊所送来的单子 写得很清楚
Yeah, it's here in the paperwork we got from the clinic.
- 没有人告诉过你吗？ - 好像没有
- Did anybody tell you?    - I don't think so.
不过他们提到说有两个心跳
Although, they did mention something about two heartbeats...
但我以为是我的和宝宝的
...but I thought that was just mine and the baby's.
他们老是说 "两个心跳都很强"
They said, "Both heartbeats are strong."
我便想 "那很好 因为我怀了个宝宝"
And I thought, "Well, that's good, because I'm having a baby."
- 太不可思议了   - 我的家族有很多对双胞胎
- This is unbelievable.    - Twins actually run in my family.
真有意思
Interesting.
我可以和你谈一下吗？
Can I see you for a second?
- 我们怎么办？ - 什么意思"我们怎么办？"
- What do we do?    - What do you mean, "What do we do?"
双胞胎
Twins!
- 钱德 你慌了  - 那你和我一起慌 不行吗？
- Chandler, you're panicking.    - Uh-huh! Join me, won't you?
咱们留下一个 另外一个让人领养 如何？
What do you say we keep one and then just have an option on the other one?
- 我们不能将他们分开   - 为什么不？
- We can't split them up.    - Why not?
我们各给他们半个金牌…
We could give each of them half a medallion.
几年过后 他们再互相找寻彼此…
And then years later, they'll find each other...
相认团圆 那一天大家将皆大欢喜
...and be reunited. I mean, that's a great day for everybody.
万一领养另一个宝宝的人很坏 怎么办？
Okay. What if the person who adopts the other one is horrible?
也有可能不会啊 万一他被国王领养了呢？
What if they're not? What if it's adopted by a king?
是啊 听说有个国王正打算领养宝宝
Yeah. Because I hear the king is looking to adopt.
摩妮卡 我们根本没准备好 要养两个孩子
Monica, we are not ready to have two babies.
那不重要 我们企盼这一刻已经很久了
That doesn't matter. We have waited so long for this.
我才不在乎是两个宝宝 三个宝宝
I don't care if it's two babies. I don't care if it's three babies.
或是一"拖拉库"的宝宝
I don't care if the entire cast of Eight Is Enough comes out of there.
我们要把他们带回家 因为他们是我们的孩子
We are taking them home because they are our children.
好吧
Okay. Shh.
- 好    - 好
- Qkay    - Qkay!
好啦
Okay.
差不多要开始了 来吧 艾瑞卡
It looks like we're about ready over here. Come on, Erica.
再开始用力
Start pushing again now.
- 她来了   - 她？是个女孩？
- Here she comes.    - She? It's a girl?
是的
Yeah.
现在我们两种都有了
Well, now we have one of each.
这就够了
And that's enough.
（中央咖啡厅）
然后她便说 这是最理想的道别方式
And then she said it was the perfect way to say goodbye.
喔 天啊
Oh, my God.
那你怎么说？
What did you say?
- 什么也没说 要怎么说呢？ - 你得告诉她你的感受啊
- Nothing. What do you say to that?    - Ross, you've got to tell her how you feel.
- 不行   - 你不能就这样放弃啊
- No way.    - Well, you can't just give up.
恐龙会这么做吗？
Is that what a dinosaur would do?
- 什么？ - 我只是想借用你的术语说明
- What?    - I'm just trying to speak your language.
罗斯 瑞秋不晓得你有心复合
Ross, Rachel doesn't know that you even wanna get back together.
如果她知道的话 她或许会改变想法 她或许不会离开
If she did, she might feel differently. She might not even go.
- 你真这么想？ - 真的啦
- You really think so?    - I'm telling you!
这里就好像在歌舞剧里会开始 唱很振奋人心的歌曲
Oh, okay, this is the part of the musical where there'd be a good, convincing song.
不要采取任何一个答案
Don't take no for an answer
不要让爱飞走
Don't let love fly away
- 嗨    - 难道我不能好好把一首歌唱完？
- Hi.   - Can't a girl finish a song around here?
- 嘿   - 嗨 我刚把艾玛送到我妈那儿
- Hey.    - Hi. So I dropped Emma off at my mom's.
- 好的   - 你今晚不带她去？
- Okay.    - You're not taking her tonight?
不 我们决定我先过去安顿
No, we decided that I'd go ahead and set up first...
星期天我妈再带艾玛去巴黎
...then my mom would bring Emma to Paris on Sunday.
带宝宝坐八小时飞机？祝她好运罗
Wow. Eight-hour flight with a baby. Good luck, Mom.
你开玩笑吧？听我妈大谈"阿金减肥" 应该要祝艾玛好运才是
Are you kidding? Eight hours with my mom talking about Atkins. Good luck, Emma.
好吧 你们说得没错 我至少应该告诉她我的感受
All right. You know what? You're right. I should at least tell her how I feel.
- 罗斯 等一下 等等   - 什么？什么？
- Ross. Wait, wait.    - What? What?
可不可以帮我买个马芬松糕？
Could you get me a muffin?
- 瑞秋？ - 怎样？
- Rachel?    - Yeah?
我知道你今晚启程 但我必须对你说…
I know you're leaving tonight, but I just have to tell you.
我爱你
I love you.
不晓得这会不会让你改变计划…
Now, I don't know if that changes your plans at all.
但…我想应该让你知道
But I thought you should know.
阿甘…
Gunther.
我也爱你 不过不是那种爱
I love you too. Probably not in the same way.
但我真的爱你 当我在咖啡店喝咖啡…
But I do. And when I'm in a café having coffee...
或看到头发比太阳还耀眼的男人…
...or I see a man with hair brighter than the sun...
我会想到你的
...I'll think of you.
- 再见 各位   - 再见
- Bye, you guys.    - Bye.
喔 我的天啊
Qh, my God!
真不可思议
Unbelievable.
- 你知道该怎么做吗？ - 我才不帮你买马芬松糕
- Hey, you know what might help?    - I'm not getting you a muffin!
他们在妈妈肚子里认得出彼此吗？
Do you think they recognize each other from in there?
或许吧 除非他们就像那种…
Maybe. Unless they're like people who've lived in apartments...
住对面公寓好几年的邻居 结果有天他们穿过阴道…
...next to each other for years, then one day they're pushed through a vagina...
终于相遇
...and they meet.
我们要带艾瑞卡到恢复室了
We're going to take Erica to Recovery now.
有件事我们想告诉你…
There's something that we wanted to tell you.
我们决定替女儿取名为艾瑞卡
We decided to name the girl baby Erica.
喔 天啊 跟我的名字一样耶
Oh, my God, that's just like my name!
是啊 没错
Son of a gun, it is.
好吧 我要去休息了
Anyway, I'm gonna go get some rest.
我很高兴我选上你们 你们会是很棒的父母
I'm really glad I picked you guys. You're gonna make great parents.
钱德也会是
Even Chandler.
- 好吧 再会了   - 再见
- Okay, well, bye.    - Bye.
- 我们再打电话给你   - 好的
- We'll call you.    - Okay.
教会夏令营玩得开心喔
Have fun at church camp.
- 看看这两个小家伙    - 是啊
- Look at these little bunnies.   - I know.
你要交换吗？
You ready to trade?
- 好   - 好
- Qkay   - Qkay-
好 来…
Okay. Let's see.
- 晚点再换好了   - 好 我现在还好
- We could trade later.    - Yeah, I'm good.
- 嘿 你在忙什么？ - 做欢迎宝宝的标语
- Hey, what are you working on?    - A "welcome home" sign for the baby.
你真贴心  那是宝宝吗？
How sweet! Oh, is that the baby?
不是 我坐到油漆了
No, I sat in the paint.
- 嘿   - 你和瑞秋谈了吗？
- Hey.    - So did you talk to Rachel?
- 没有 我不打算讲   - 什么？
- No. And I'm not going to.    - What?
- 为什么不？ - 她一定会泼我冷水
- Why not?    - She's just gonna shoot me down.
你们都看到阿甘的下场了 那可一点也不好玩
You saw what happened with Gunther. That did not look like fun.
你怎么拿自己和阿甘比？
How can you compare yourself to Gunther?
对啦 他是比较性感没错…
I mean, sure, he's sexy in a more obvious way.
你和她关系匪浅 你昨晚还和她上了床
You have a relationship with her. You slept together last night.
是啊 而她还是要走 她的立场再清楚不过了
Yeah, and she still wants to go. It's pretty clear where she is.
我懂你的意思… 有时候…
Yeah, I know what you mean. I mean, sometimes...
- 乔伊   - 讨厌
- Uh, Joe.    - Damn it!
即便我想告诉她 也不用现在讲啊
If I were gonna tell her, I don't have to do it now.
我还会再见到她 有的是时间
Okay? I'll be seeing her again. We've got time.
不 你没时间了 她就要去巴黎 去认识别人了
No, you don't. She's going to Paris! She is going to meet somebody.
你可知那里有多少大帅哥？整座城都是阿甘
Do you know how many hot guys there are in Paris? It's a city of Gunthers.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.    - Hey.
- 你手上拿了什么？ - 喔 我做了一点东西
- What do you have there? - Oh, I made a little something.
如果我时间更充裕的话 可能会更好 但是…
If I had more time to work on it, it'd be better, but...
(欢迎降临世界 宾宝宝)
- 天啊 你自己做的吗？ - 亲爱的 棒极了
- Oh, my God, you did that yourself? - Honey, that's gorgeous.
你知道 宝宝不识字的 麦克
You know, the baby can't read, Mike.
接的车已经到了 他们怎么还没回来呢？
Hi. The car service just got here. I can't believe they're not home yet!
我得去赶飞机 我想见见宝宝啊
I have to catch my stupid plane. I want to see the baby.
摩妮卡刚从计程车上打电话来说 他们就快到了
Monica just called from the cab. She said they should be here any minute.
- 好像会有个大惊喜    - 她口气有没有很高兴？
- Apparently, there's some big surprise.     - Yeah, did she sound happy about it?
因为我朋友依莎的宝宝刚出生时 有小胡须呢
Because my friend Ethel's baby was born with a teeny-tiny beard.
- 欢迎回家  - 喔 天啊
- Welcome home. - Oh, my God.
- 喔 我的天  - 嘿
- Oh, my gosh. - Hey.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 大惊喜究竟是什么？
Hey, so, what is the big surprise?
- 喔 我的天啊  - 这怎么可能…？
- Oh, my God! - How did this...?
请恕我冒昧… 医院知道你们抱两个回家吧？
Okay, awkward question. The hospital knows you took two, right?
- 知道 是双胞胎    - 喔 天…他们好可爱喔
- Yes. It's twins.     - Oh, my... They are so cute.
- 他们是男生还是女生？ - 这个是男孩 那个是女孩
- Now, what kinds are they?     - This is a boy. And that's a girl.
她名字叫艾瑞卡
Her name is Erica.
嘿 那个孕母的名字也叫艾瑞卡
Hey, that pregnant girl's name was Erica.
真可惜你们俩 没多花点时间在一起
Yeah. It's a shame you two didn't get to spend more time together.
是啊 我们帮男孩取名为杰克 跟爸爸一样
Yeah, and we named the boy Jack, after Dad.
- 他一定会很高兴的    - 杰克宾…我喜欢
- He's gonna be so happy.     - Jack Bing. I love that.
听起来像四十年代的新闻播报员 "杰克宾 晨间特报…
It sounds like a '40s newspaper guy. You know, "Jack Bing, Morning Gazette.
我将为您揭发大新闻"
I'm gonna blow this story wide open."
喔 天啊…
Oh, my gosh.
- 好漂亮喔   - 我也想要- 个
- So beautiful.     - I want one.
是吗？告诉我你想要哪个 我偷偷把它藏在外套里
Oh, yeah? Well, tell me which one. I'll try to slip it in my coat.
说正经的 你想要一个吗？
Seriously. I mean, you want to make one of those?
- 一个？- 大堆如何？ - 真的？
- One? How about a whole bunch?     - Really?
是啊 我们可以教他们唱歌 组成像《真善美》里的家庭乐团
Yeah. We can teach them to sing, and we could be like the von Trapp family.
除去纳粹那一部分 但那又有点平淡无奇
Only without the Nazis. Although that sounds kind of dull.
真是的 我再不走的话 我就要错过班机了
I can't believe this. If I don't leave now, I'm gonna miss my plane.
- 我真高兴你能看到宝宝们    - 我也是
- I'm so glad you got to see the babies.     - Me too.
真是遗憾 我不能留在这儿 看你们俩手忙脚乱应付他们
I'm just sorry I'm not gonna be around to watch you two attempt to handle this.
好吧 我不能再跟你们道别了
All right. Oh, I can't say goodbye to you guys again.
- 我爱你们全部    - 爱你
- I love you all so much.     - Love you.
- 我们爱你    - 到了打电话给我们
- We love you.     - Call us when you get there.
我会的 罗斯 过来…
I will. Ross, come here.
我只想让你知道…
I just want you to know...
昨晚…
...last night...
我永远不会忘记的
...I'll never forget it.
我也不会
Neither will I.
好了 我真的该走了
All right. Now I really have to go.
好吧 再会了
Okay, au revoir.
额
Ugh.
那里的人一定会恨死我的
They're gonna really hate me over there.
你就这样让她走了？
So you just let her go?
是啊
Yeah.
- 嘿 或许这样最好吧    - 是吗？
- Hey, maybe that's for the best.     - Yeah?
是啊 你知道…你就… 听着 你必须…
Yeah. You know, you just... Look, you gotta...
你必须以她的角度看待昨晚的事
You gotta think about last night the way she does.
你知道 或许…
Okay? You know, maybe...
或许上床是最理想的道别方式
Maybe sleeping together was the perfect way to say goodbye.
- 现在她永远也不晓得他的感受   - 或许那没关系 你知道吗？
- But now she'll never know how he feels.     - Maybe that's okay, you know?
或许这样比较好
Maybe it is better this way.
我是说 现在… 现在你便能继续过你的日子
I mean, now... Now you can move on.
你已经尝试了这么久
I mean, you've been trying to for so long.
现在你或许已经到达不同"洲"了…
Maybe now that you're on different continents...
- 对吧？ - 耶
- Right?     - Yeah.
或许你现在已经能够应付了
Maybe now you can actually do it, you know.
你终于能够忘了她
You can finally get over her.
是啊 没错
Yeah, that's true.
只是…
Except.
- 我不想忘了她   - 什么？
- I don't want to get over her.     - What?
- 我不想 我想和她在一起   - 真的？
- I don't. I want to be with her.     - Really?
- 是的 我要去追她    - 是的 你必须
- Yeah. I'm going to go after her.     - Yeah, you are!
等等 等等  你的外套啊 你的外套
Wait! Wait! Get your coat! Get your coat!
- 我的外套    - 太酷了
- My coat.     - This is so cool!
我不晓得到底是怎么回事 但我好兴奋喔
I have no idea what's going on, but I am excited!
- 罗斯 你想她会怎么说？ - 不晓得
- What do you think she's gonna say?     - I don't know.
即便她泼我冷水 至少我下半辈子不用花时间猜想…
But even if she shoots me down, at least I won't spend my life wondering...
可能会怎样… 我的外套咧？
...what would have happened. Where is my coat?
你没带外套啦 我的车在楼下 我载你去机场
You didn't bring one! My cab's downstairs. I'll drive you to the airport.
- 祝我好运   - 快点啦
- Wish me luck.     - Hurry!
祝你好运
Good luck!
- 怎么没有安全带？ - 没关系 万一撞到东西的话…
- There's no seat belts!     - That's okay. If we hit anything...
引擎会爆炸 所以被弹出车外会比较安全
...the engine will explode, so it's better if you're thrown from the car.
- 好了 好了 出发吧    - 好的
- All right, all right. Let's do this.     - Okay!
- 嘿    - 到80街和东瑞卫路口
- Hey!     - 80th and East End.
- 不 我不载客   - 法律规定你不能拒载短程
- No. I don't take passengers.     - The law makes you accept any fare.
你不懂啦 这不是真的计程车
You don't understand. This cab isn't real.
你的计程车牌几号？
What's your medallion number?
我的计程车牌照号码是… "给我滚下车"
My medallion number is, get out of the cab!
- 什么？ - 滚下车去
- What?     - Get out of the cab!
喔 嘿 我可以给你们 我准备的乔迁之礼吗？
Oh, hey, can I give you guys your housewarming gift now?
- 当然可以   - 好吧…
- Now, that you can do.     - All right.
小鸡鸡？小鸭鸭？
Chick Jr.? Duck Jr.?
别躲着你们的妈妈
Don't hide from Mama!
你现在可以张开眼睛了
You can open your eyes now.
- 我们过桥了吗？ - 过了啦
- Are we off the bridge?    - Yes!
- 那个骑脚踏车的女人还活着吗？ - 是的 她很快又跳上车了
- Is the old woman on the bicycle still alive?     - Yeah, she jumped right back up.
- 喔 老天 菲比 慢一点    - 你到底想不想及时拦住瑞秋？
- Oh, my God. Phoebe, slow down!     - Do you want to get to Rachel in time?
想啊 但我可不想死在 你的计程车里
Yes, but I don't want to die in your cab.
你上车之前就应该想到
You should have thought of that before you got in!
- 收费站   - 什么？
- Tollbooth.     - What?
收费站
Toll booth !
四块钱 置物箱里有零钱
Four bucks. There are quarters in the glove compartment.
快点
Hurry!
好…
Okay. Aah!
哇 车窗怎么这么干净
Damn, that window's clean.
呱 呱 啼 啼 呱 呱
Quack, quack. Tweet, tweet. Quack, quack.
啼 啼 呱 呱
Tweet, tweet. Quack, quack.
啼 啼 呱 呱…
Tweet, tweet. Quack, quack. Tweet, tweet. Quack, tweet, quack.
我们在想 为什么拿个礼物拿这么久…
We were wondering what was taking so long...
现在我们了解了 你是在忙"这个"
...but now we understand. You were doing this.
好吧 我想要给你们一个惊喜 可是…
Okay. I wanted to surprise you, but...
你们的乔迁之礼 我准备了一只小鸡和一只小鸭
For your housewarming gift, I got you a baby chick and a baby duck.
真的？你要送我们 一只小鸡和一只小鸭？
Really? You got us a chick and a duck?
棒极了 正合有新生儿的新房子… 鸡鸭屎
Oh, great. Just what you want for a new house with infants. Bird feces!
他们大概从桌子上跳下来 不见踪影了
But they must've jumped off the table. Now they're gone!
别担心 会找到他们的
Don't worry, we'll find them.
- 我要去看看双胞胎  - 好吧
- I'm gonna go check on the twins. - All right.
喔 天啊  我踩到了什么东西？
Oh, God! What did I just step on?
- 没关系 只是春卷而已   - 哦
- It's okay. It's just an egg roll.     - Oh.
你踩到我的春卷？
You stepped on my egg roll?
对不起 我不晓得走路 还要看地上有没有中国菜
I'm sorry. I didn't know to look for Chinese food on the floor.
把它放在盘子里 然后离开
Just put it on a plate and leave.
- 我们来找鸡甲鸟吧    - 好吧
- Okay. Let's find these birds.     - All right.
等等 等等 你听到了吗？
Wait, wait. You hear that?
- 他们在桌子里    - 那可大不妙
- They're in the table!     - Well, that can't be good.
- 我们得把他们弄出来  - 怎么弄？
- We gotta get them out of there!     - How?
或许可以把他们骗出来 你会学鸟叫吗？
Maybe we can lure them out. You know any birdcalls?
会很多种呢 我可是高手
Oh, tons. I'm quite the Woodsman.
我们可以将桌子往一边倾斜
Well, maybe we can just tip the table a little.
乔伊 等一下  球啊
Joey, wait! The ball!
我们该怎么办？
So, what do we do?
或许可以把它打开
Maybe we can open this up somehow.
好吧
Okay.
不行…全都黏死了
No. It's all glued together.
难道我们要把它撬开吗？
Does that mean we have to bust it open?
- 不晓得 大概吧    - 喔 天啊
- I don't know. Maybe.     - Oh, my God.
我知道 这… 这是手足球桌…
I know. it's... It's the foosball table.
好吧 你知道吗？我们别无选择
All right, you know what? We don't have a choice.
就像我在那部科幻片里说的台词 如果当初是由我来演的话…
It's like I would have said in that sci-fi movie if I'd have gotten the part.
里面是咱们的同胞 我们得将他们救出来
Those are our men in there, and we have to get them out...
即便我得牺牲我生命中 最重要的东西…
...even if I have to sacrifice the most important thing in my life...
我的时光机器
...my time machine.
- 那部电影拍成了吗？ - 没拍成
- Did that movie ever get made?     - It did not.
杰克温伯 请接白色专线电话 杰克温伯
Jack Weinberg, white courtesy phone. Jack Weinberg.
- 罗斯 你要去哪？ - 去找瑞秋啊
- Ross, where are you going?     - Uh, to talk to Rachel.
这不是我们搭 亡命计程车的原因吗？
Isn't that why we took a ride in the death cab?
你打算追到登机门？
You're walking up to her at the gate?
你难道都没在机场追过人吗？
Have you never chased anyone through the airport before?
自警网节目停播之后就没有了
Not since my cop show got canceled.
你得先买张机票才过得了安全检查
You have to get a ticket to get past security.
- 什么？那样永远也追不上  - 那种态度怎么追得上 快点啦
- What? We're never gonna make it.     - Not with that attitude. Now, haul ass!
你们可以走得再慢一点
Okay, if you could all walk slower, that'd be great.
- 小姐 请出示你的护照   - 喔 天啊
- Madame, your passport, please.     - Oh, my God.
我正在担心 我不太记得高中时学的法文
I was afraid I wouldn't remember any of my high school French.
不过 我完全知道你在讲什么
But I understood every word you just said.
- 请出示你的登机证 - 喔 好的
- Your boarding pass, please. - Oh, sure.
哦
Oh...
糟糕 我明明有的 我真不敢相信
Shoot, I had it. Oh, I can't believe this.
- 小姐 如果你没有你的…   - 我有啦 我有啦
- Madame, if you don't have your...   - I have it, I have it!
哦
Oh...
好吧 我找不到 可是我记得我的座位是3 ZC…
Okay, I can't find it, but I remember that I was in seat 32C...
因为那是我的胸罩尺寸
...because that's my bra size.
你必须要有你的登机证…
You must have your boarding pass...
如果我是36D的话 你一定不会找我麻烦
You know what? If I was in 36D, we would not be having this problem.
- 嗨 我要买一张票   - 只买一张？
- Hi. I need a ticket.     - Just one?
我载你来 就不能看看事情发展经过吗？
I drive you here, and I don't get to see how it works out?
- 好吧 两张票 我要买两张票   - 我们要去度蜜月
- Fine. Two tickets. I need two tickets.     - We're on our honeymoon.
- 目的地是？ - 随便 哪里最便宜就去哪
- And the destination?    - I don't care. Whatever's the cheapest.
嫁给你我真走运
I'm so lucky I married you.
喔  要命  到底在哪里？
Oh, shoot. Damn it. Where is it?
找到了 找到了 我就说我找得到…
I found it. I found it. I told you I would find it.
拿去吧  你不是刚刚那个人
In your face. You're a different person.
对不起
Sorry.
好 往巴黎421号班机
Okay. Flight 421, Paris.
- 我没看到 你看到了吗？ - 没有 我们错过了吗？
- I don't see it. Do you see it?     - No. Did we miss it?
不 不可能啊 还有二十分钟才起飞啊
No, no, it's impossible. It doesn't leave for another 20 minutes.
我们或许搞错班机号码了
Maybe we have the flight number wrong.
天啊
God.
- 哈罗   - 嘿 是我 罗斯要跟你说…
- Hello.     - Hey, it's me. Here's Ross.
什么？
What?
嘿 听着…
Hey. Hey, listen...
双胞胎发出的声音好可爱喔 等一下 你听…
You wouldn't believe the cute noises the twins are making. Wait, listen.
摩妮卡…
But Monica...
摩妮卡 摩妮卡 摩妮卡
Monica. Monica. Monica. Monica.
真抱歉 他们刚刚有发出声的
I'm sorry. They were doing it before.
- 没关系 听着…   - 喔 等一下 他们又来了
- That's all right. Listen, listen.     - Oh, wait, wait. Here they go again.
摩妮卡 摩妮卡 摩妮卡
Monica. Monica. Monica. Monica.
- 摩妮卡？ - 是不是很可爱呢？
- Monica?     - Isn't that cute?
可爱的不得了  听着…
That is precious! Listen...
- 我要瑞秋的班机资料   - 喔 好的…
- I need Rachel's flight information.     - Oh, okay.
- 是421号班机 8点40分起飞   - 但时刻表上面没有这一班啊
- All right, it's flight 421. Leaves at 8:40.     - I have that. It's not on the board.
421号班机 8点40分离开纽渥克机场
That's what it says here. Flight 421. Leaves at 8:40. Newark Airport.
- 什么？ - 纽渥克机场
- What?     - Newark Airport.
- 为什么？你们在哪？ - 甘乃迪机场
- Why? Where are you?     - JFK.
别担心 我们会救你们出来的
Don't worry, you guys! We're gonna get you out of there!
我们也会帮你们买小小助听器的
And we're also gonna buy you tiny bird hearing aids.
好了 开始了…
Okay. Here goes.
怎么回事？
What's the matter?
我得先和这桌子道别
I need to say goodbye to the table first.
我了解…
I understand.
好吧
Okay.
桌子啊…
Table...
你为我们带来许多美好时光
...you have given us so many great times.
还有你们… 乔登 维特 乔…
And you guys, Jordan, Victor, Joel...
你们大家… 我能说什么呢？
All of you guys. What can I say?
你们让我们很有面子
You guys make us look good.
- 你想说什么吗？ - 不晓得
- You want to say anything?     - I don't know.
除了 再讲最后一次…
Except that, for one last time...
打得好 打得好 打得好
Good game. Good game. Good game.
- 打得好   - 耶
- Good game.     - Yeah.
好了 开始了
Okay. Here we go.
我下不了手
I can't do it.
我也下不了手
Well, I can't do it either.
- 嘿 你们找到了吗？ - 找到了 困在这桌子里
- Hey. Did you find them?    - Yeah. They're stuck inside the table.
必须撬开桌子 但我们俩都下不了手
And we have to bust it open, but neither of us can do it.
当然啦 一定会很难下手
Oh, well, sure. It's got to be so hard.
我来吧 给我
I'll do it. Give me.
菲比 不要 不要 不要
Phoebe! No, no, no!
哇 我从来没开这么快过
Wow, I've never gone this fast before.
菲比 算了 好吧？纽渥克还有一个小时车程
Phoebe, forget it, okay? Newark is, like, an hour away.
我们绝对赶不到的
There's no way we'll make it in time.
- 她有带手机 你可以打电话给她    - 我不要用电话讲
- She's got her cell. You could call her.     - I am not doing this over the phone.
你没有其他选择了
You don't have any other choice.
- 喂？ - 瑞秋 喔 太好了
- Hello?    - Rachel. Oh, good.
你刚刚上飞机了吗？
By the way, did you just get on the plane?
- 是的   - 我们原本追得到她的…
- Yeah.     - We would have caught her...
- 如果我们跑对机场的话    - 吖
-...if we were at the right airport.     - Yay.
瑞秋 等一下
Um, Rachel, hang on.
不要 不要 不要
No. No. No.
菲比 一切都还好吧？
Phoebe, is everything okay?
额
Um...
事实上 不太好 你必须下飞机
Actually, no. No. You have to get off the plane.
- 什么？为什么？ - 我有个感觉…
- What? Why?     - I have this feeling that...
那架飞机不太对劲 它的左趾骨那里有问题
...something's wrong with it. Something is wrong with the left phalange.
亲爱的 我确信这飞机没问题啦
Oh, honey, I'm sure there's nothing wrong with the plane.
听着 我要挂了 我爱你 我一到巴黎就打给你
Look, I have to go. I love you, and I will call you the minute I get to Paris.
额
Um, ahem...
- 怎么回事？ - 我一个疯疯癫癫的朋友
- What was that?     - Oh, that was just my crazy friend.
她叫我下飞机 因为她感觉…
She told me to get off the plane because she had a "feeling" that there...
什么左趾骨那里有问题
...was something wrong with the left phalange.
- 那听起来挺糟糕的    - 我才不担心呢
- Okay. Uh, that doesn't sound good.     - Oh, I wouldn't worry about it.
她经常讲这些有的没的 很少被她说中过
She comes up with this stuff, and she's almost never right.
- 但偶尔会被她说中   - 这个嘛…
- But she is sometimes.     - Well...
- 你在干什么？ - 我不要坐这架飞机了
- What are you doing?     - I can't take this plane now.
- 对不起 先生 你要去哪？ - 我要下飞机
- Excuse me, sir. Where are you going?     - I have to get off this plane.
她朋友感应到 飞机的左趾骨出了问题
Her friend has a feeling something's wrong with the left phalange.
能给我一点花生吗？
Could I get some peanuts?
- 这架飞机有什么问题？ - 没有问题
- What's wrong with the plane?     - There's nothing wrong.
- 左趾骨   - 哪有什么"趾骨"
- The left phalange.     - There's no "phalange."
天啊 这架飞机居然连趾骨都没有
Oh, my God. This plane doesn't even have a phalange.
- 那我也不要坐   - 小姐 请坐下
- I'm not flying on it.     - Please sit down.
- 发生什么事了？ - 我们要下飞机 这飞机没有趾骨
- What's going on'?     - We're getting off. There is no phalange!
真是太荒谬了 我…
This is ridiculous. I...
是呀 好吧
Yeah, okay.
好了 我的任务已完成
All right. My job here is done.
真令人刮目相看
That was impressive.
是呀 你大部分时间 甚至都没用到工具
Yeah. You didn't even use the tools for most of it.
是啊 用工具太慢了
Yeah, they were just slowing me down.
好了 我要去看宝宝 回头见 你们两个娘子军
All right. I gotta get back to the babies. See you girls later.
- 这桌子…真是遗憾啊   - 是呀
- Sorry about the table, man.     - Yeah.
你要买台新的吗？
You gonna buy a new one?
大概不了
Probably not. No.
你搬走以后 我大概也不会很想玩了
I don't know how much I'm gonna want to play after you go.
- 至少我们救出这些小家伙   - 是啊
- Well, at least we got these little guys out.     - Yeah.
我们很担心你们呢
Aw, we were worried about you.
嗯
Hm.
我最好习惯有东西在我手上大便 是吧？
I guess I better get used to things crapping in my hand, huh?
我会想念这两个小家伙
I'm gonna miss these little guys.
能再次有小鸡小鸭陪伴感觉真好
It was nice having birds around again.
嘿 你知道吗？或许应该把他们留在这儿
Hey, you know what? Maybe we should keep them here with you.
- 什么？ - 是啊 我们现在手边这么多事
- What?     - Yeah. We got a lot going on right now.
再说 他们在这里还有自己的房间
And plus, here, they'd have their own room.
我还可以再养一只鹅
I could get a goose!
你现在家禽类全都包办了
You know, I think you're set with the poultry.
谢了 老兄 你们听到了吗 小家伙？
Thanks, man. You hear that, you guys?
你们要留在这里 那很好…
You're gonna get to stay here. And it's good...
你知道 因为…
...you know, because, uh...
因为你这样就有理由来看我了
Because now you have a reason to come visit.
或许还会有其他理由
I think there may be another reason.
所以…
So, uh...
来个尴尬的拥抱 还是整脚的酷哥式握手？
Awkward hug or lame cool-guy handshake?
好啊…那就整脚的酷哥式握手好了
Yeah, well, you know, lame cool-guy handshake.
- 小姐 我跟你保证这飞机没问题   - 你们修理好趾骨了吗？
- Ma'am, I assure you, the plane is fine.     - And you fixed the phalange?
是的 趾骨已经修好了
Yes. The phalange's fixed.
事实上 我们还加了好多趾骨上去 以防万一
In fact, we've put a whole lot of extra phalanges on board, just in case.
呼叫安德森先生 乔许安德森先生
Paging Mr. Anderson. Mr. Josh Anderson.
- 她在哪？ - 我没看到她
- Where is she?     - I don't see her.
- 瑞秋 瑞秋葛林  - 她在那儿
- Rachel! Rachel Green!     - There she is!
瑞秋 瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel!
- 喂 你有登机证吗？ - 没有 我只想和某人说话
- Whoa, do you have a boarding pass?     - No. I just have to talk to someone.
对不起 没有登机证你不能进去
I'm sorry. You need a boarding pass.
- 不行啊 你不…    - 瑞秋
- No, no. But you don't...     - Rachel!
什么？喔 天啊 你们在这里做什么？
What? Oh, my God. What are you guys doing here?
好 该你上了
Okay. You're on.
什么事？怎么了 罗斯？你吓到我了 怎么回事？
What? What, Ross? Okay, you're scaring me. What's going on?
- 好 是这样的…   - 怎样…
- Okay. Thing is...     - Yeah.
- 别走   - 什么？
- Don't go.     - What?
求求你留在我身边 我深爱你 请你别走
Please, please stay with me. I am so in love with you. Please don't go.
- 喔 我的天啊   - 我知道 我知道
- Oh, my God.     - I know. I know.
我不应该等到现在才讲 可是…那很蠢 好吧？对不起
I shouldn't have waited till now to say it, but, um... That was stupid, okay? I'm sorry.
可是我现在要告诉你 我爱你
But I'm telling you now. I love you.
- 别上飞机   - 小姐 你要上飞机吗？
- Do not get on this plane.     - Miss, are you boarding the plane?
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey
我知道你爱我 我知道的
I know you love me. I know you do.
- 小姐…   - 我…
- Miss     - I...
我…我得上飞机了
I... I have to get on the plane.
- 不 你不行    - 我必须去
- No, you don't.     - Yes, I do.
- 不 你不行  - 我得去 他们在等我啊 罗斯
- No, you don't.     - I do. They're waiting for me, Ross.
我现在不能这么做 对不起 对不起
I can't do this right now, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
瑞秋…
Rachel.
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我真的以为她会留下来
I really thought she'd stay.
我知道…
I know.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
就这样罗
Well, that's it.
所有东西都打包了
Everything's packed.
哇哦
Wow.
- 感觉好奇怪   - 是啊
- This is weird.     - I know.
是啊
Yeah.
这表示没东西吃了吗？
Uh, does this mean there's nothing to eat?
我放了三份千层面在你的冷冻库里
I put three lasagnas in your freezer.
我爱你
I love you.
- 嘿   - 嘿 你们有赶上吗？
- Hey.     - Hey. Did you guys make it in time?
有 他和她讲到话了 但她还是上了飞机
Yeah, yeah. He talked to her, but, um, she got on the plane anyway.
罗斯人呢？
Where's Ross?
他回家了 他不想见任何人
He went home. He didn't want to see anybody.
罗斯 嗨 是我
Ross. Hi, it's me.
我刚回到飞机上 我感觉糟透了…
I just got back on the plane, and I just feel awful.
我真的不希望 我们在这种情况下分手
That is so not how I wanted things to end with us.
只是我没想到会看到你…
It's just that I wasn't expecting to see you.
你突然间冒出来 还讲了那些话…
And all of a sudden you're there and saying these things.
现在我坐在这儿想着…
Now I'm just sitting here and thinking...
所有该说却没有说的话…
...of all the stuff I should have said and I didn't.
我甚至都没告诉你 我也爱你
I mean, I didn't even get to tell you that I love you too.
因为 我当然是爱你的
Because of course I do. I love you.
我爱你
I love you.
我在干嘛？我爱你
What am I doing? I love you.
我得见你 我得离开这架飞机
I've got to see you. I've got to get off this plane.
喔 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 好 对不起…   - 小姐 请坐下
- Okay, excuse me.     - Miss, please sit down.
不 对不起 真的很抱歉 我必须下飞机
No, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry, but I need to get off the plane.
- 我必须告诉某人我爱他   - 我不能让你下飞机
- I need to tell someone that I love them.     - I can't let you off.
放她下飞机
Let her off the plane!
你必须坐在座位上
You have to take your seat.
喔 求求你 小姐 你不了解啊
Oh, please, miss. You don't understand.
试着将心比心啊
Try to understand!
拜托你 小姐 有没有办法可以让我下…？
Come on, miss, isn't there any way that you can just let me off the...?
不 不
No! No!
喔 天啊 她下飞机了吗？她下飞机了吗？
Oh, my God. Did she get off the plane? Did she get off the plane?
我下了飞机
I got off the plane.
你下了飞机
You got off the plane.
我真的爱你
I do love you.
我也爱你 我再也不让你离开了
I love you too, and I am never letting you go again.
那好 因为这里是我想要的地方 再不三心两意了
Okay. Because this is where I want to be. Okay? No more messing around.
- 我再也不要搞砸了   - 我也是 我们的傻日子结束了
- I don't want to mess this up again.     - Me neither. We're done being stupid.
好 就你和我 好吧？就这样
Okay. It's you and me, all right? This is it.
就这样 除了我们分开的时候
This is it. Unless we're on a break.
现在别开玩笑
Don't make jokes now.
请小心一点 那是我外婆的 小心点
Okay, please be careful with that. It was my grandmother's. Be careful.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果这从卡车上掉出去的话 没关系的
If that falls off the truck, it wouldn't be the worst thing.
哇
Wow.
我知道…
I know.
感觉上变小了
Seems smaller somehow.
那个一直都是紫色的吗？
Has it always been purple?
你们看看这里… 这里是你们第一个家
Look around, you guys. This was your first home.
这曾经是个快乐的地方 充满着爱与欢笑
And it was a happy place, filled with love and laughter.
但更重要的是 因为房租管制法 这里房租便宜得要命
But more important, because of rent control, it was a frigging steal.
你们知道吗 我们几个 全都住过这间公寓呢？
Hey, do you realize that, at one time or another, we all lived in this apartment?
是啊 没错
Oh, yeah. That's true.
我没有…
Uh, I haven't.
有 大学时 你和外婆住的那个暑假…
What about that summer during college that you lived with Grandma...
你还想当舞者呢？
...and you tried to make it as a dancer?
你可知这件事被刻意隐藏 几乎十年了？
Do you realize we almost made it 10 years without that coming up?
亲爱的 我忘了 我答应过崔格要留下钥匙
Oh, honey, I forgot. I promised Treeger that we'd leave our keys.
喔 好的
Oh, okay.
- 所以就这样罗   - 是啊
- So I guess this is it.     - Yeah.
大概吧
I guess so.
这比我想像的还要难
This is harder than I thought it would be.
喔 一切都会没事的
Oh, it's gonna be okay.
走吧
Come on.
你们现在要回家了吗 有没有一点时间？
Do you guys have to go to the new house now, or do you have some time?
我们有时间啊
We got some time.
- 我们去喝点咖啡好不好？ - 当然好
- Okay. Should we get some coffee?     - Sure.
到哪呢？
Where?